export const quizData = [
  {
    question: "Which 'F' is a flat savoury Italian bread?",
    answers: ["Formaggio", "Focaccia", "Figa", "Fusilli"],
    correctAnswer: "Focaccia"
  },
  {
    question: "What country produces the most potatoes?",
    answers: ["China", "United States", "Ireland", "Russia"],
    correctAnswer: "China"
  },
  {
    question:
      "In the drink called a zombie, what is the main alcoholic ingredient?",
    answers: ["Beer", "Brandy", "Rum", "Whiskey"],
    correctAnswer: "Rum"
  },
  {
    question: "Marzipan is made with what kind of nut?",
    answers: ["Almond", "Cashew", "Pecan", "Walnut"],
    correctAnswer: "Almond"
  },
  {
    question: "In French cooking, what does 'en Croute' mean?",
    answers: ["In Sauce", "In Oven", "In a bowl", "In Pastry"],
    correctAnswer: "In Pastry"
  },
  {
    question: "Which 'C' is a thick fish or seafood soup",
    answers: ["Ceviche", "Chub", "Chowder", "Crabcakes"],
    correctAnswer: "Chowder"
  },
  {
    question: "Which 'P' is a quill-shaped Italian pasta?",
    answers: ["Percy Pigs", "Penne", "Pepe", "Provola"],
    correctAnswer: "Penne"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Literally meaning 'whirlpool', which German desert is thin sheet of rolled up dough baked?",
    answers: ["Strudel", "Bratwurst", "Sp√§tzle", "Gabelstapler"],
    correctAnswer: "Strudel"
  },
  {
    question: "Where was the first McDonald's restaurant located?",
    answers: ["Texas", "Kansas", "California", "Leamington Spa"],
    correctAnswer: "California"
  },
  {
    question: "What ingredient in bread causes it to rise?",
    answers: ["Yeast", "Toaster", "Flour", "Water"],
    correctAnswer: "Yeast"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Immersing food in vinegar to prolong its lifespan is known as what?",
    answers: ["Fickling", "Marinating", "Tickling", "Pickling"],
    correctAnswer: "Pickling"
  },
  {
    question:
      "The 'chips' that are commonly served with fish are made out of which vegetable?",
    answers: ["Courgettes", "Cabbage", "Potatoes", "Asparagus"],
    questions: "Potatoes"
  },
  {
    question:
      "According to legend, vampires are exceptionally vulnerable to which vegetable?",
    answers: ["Onions", "Sprouts", "Garlic", "Wayne Rooney"],
    correctAnswer: "Garlic"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Red Stripe is a popular beer brand that originates from which country?",
    answers: ["Jamaica", "United States", "Mexico", "United Kingdom"],
    correctAnswer: "Jamaica"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the most popular spice in the world",
    answers: ["Paprika", "Pepper", "Scary Spice", "Five Spice"],
    correctAnswer: "Pepper"
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is eaten traditionally in the UK the day before Ash Wednesday?",
    answers: [
      "Bubble & Squeak",
      "Full English",
      "Chocolate Orange",
      "Pancakes"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Pancakes"
  },
  {
    question: "What are dried plums called?",
    answers: ["Prunes", "Balloons", "Dried Plums", "Raisin"],
    correctAnswer: "Prunes"
  }
];
